const wordData: WordData[] = [
  {
    question: "mikroorganizm",
    answer: "a microbe",
  },
  {
    question: "to contain disease",
    answer: "pathogenic",
  },
  {
    question: "pielęgnacja",
    answer: "grooming",
  },
  {
    question: "to leave something somewhere",
    answer: "deposit something",
  },
  {
    question: "nosowy",
    answer: "nasal",
  },
  {
    question: "pokryć coś warstwą",
    answer: "coat something",
  },
  {
    question: "zawierać bakterię",
    answer: "harbour",
  },
  {
    question: "zawierać",
    answer: "to contain",
  },
  {
    question: "jest prawdopodobne, że ...",
    answer: "it is likely that ...",
  },
  {
    question: "szanse są",
    answer: "the chances are",
  },
  {
    question: "zagrożony",
    answer: "at risk",
  },
  {
    question: "wykryto",
    answer: "detected",
  },
  {
    question: "pod kontrolą",
    answer: "under scrutiny",
  },
  {
    question: '"to increase, especially an emotion or effect"',
    answer: "to heighten / heightened",
  },
  {
    question: "skłonny do",
    answer: "prone to",
  },
  {
    question: "powstrzymać się od",
    answer: "refrain from",
  },
  {
    question: "zwolnić kogoś",
    answer: "make someone redundant",
  },
  {
    question: "wziąć wolne",
    answer: "take time off",
  },
  {
    question: "zwrócić czyjąś uwagę",
    answer: "come to somebody's attention",
  },
  {
    question: "nawiązywać kontakty",
    answer: "make connections",
  },
  {
    question: "nawiązać rozmowę",
    answer: "strike up a conversation",
  },
  {
    question: "zrobić dobre wrażenie",
    answer: "make a good impression",
  },
  {
    question: "aplikować o pracę",
    answer: "apply for a job",
  },
  {
    question: "budowanie relacji",
    answer: "develop rapport",
  },
  {
    question: "nazwiazywanie kontaktów biznesowych",
    answer: "networking",
  },
  {
    question: "sieć relacji",
    answer: "web of relationships",
  },
  {
    question: "celowo",
    answer: "deliberately",
  },
  {
    question: "a digital form of money produced by a public company",
    answer: "a cryptocurrency",
  },
  {
    question: "moving and transferring illegal money to make it seem legal",
    answer: "money laundering",
  },
  {
    question: "taking something using legal authority",
    answer: "a seizure",
  },
  {
    question: "to keep something secret",
    answer: "conceal",
  },
  {
    question: "attracting a lot of attention in the media",
    answer: "high-profile",
  },
  {
    question: "a record of money received and paid",
    answer: "a ledger",
  },
  {
    question: "to build or create something again",
    answer: "reconstruct",
  },
  {
    question: "a situation where there is more effort to punish people for a specific crime",
    answer: "a crackdown",
  },
  {
    question: "a big part of the value of something",
    answer: "major contributor",
  },
  {
    question: "connected to",
    answer: "associated",
  },
  {
    question: "carry out something",
    answer: "to conduct",
  },
  {
    question: "the first stage of process",
    answer: "starting point for",
  },
  {
    question: "hidden",
    answer: "to be masked",
  },
  {
    question: "appearance or arrival of something",
    answer: "emergence of",
  },
  {
    question: "results of an action",
    answer: "implications",
  },
];

const exported: Data = {
  data: wordData,
  class: "EN",
  id: "en-hygiene-networking-bitcoin",
  title: "Hygiene, Bitcoin & Networking",
  description: "Vocabulary for a short test",
  tags: ["office", "hygiene", "bitcoin", "english"],
};

export default exported;
